location that was given a name by white people and now all of a sudden exists no before that
there was a people and we are the we are the extension of that and those white folks those
zionists those white supremacists they know that and that's why they put the most effort
into keeping black people separate and suppressed over so many centuries they're like we got to keep
shutting black people down do you understand it's not simply just about resources it's about
spirit you think they were shutting down almo car cabral and walter rodney and lumumba and
and sankara just because they were like taking their money back no it's because they were bringing
the reconnection of the black people to their power back that's why you think they murked martin luther
king and malcolm x and medgar evers because they were getting people to vote no it's because those
were people that had an alignment with a spiritual power that they saw and said we got to get it out
of here this is bigger than capitalism bro these people make money because money controls but it's
really about control the earth is a source of power and the continent that is the largest continent on
this planet had the most people that had the most knowledge of that power at one time and they came
and got all of those folks wrapped up except for ethiopia wrapped up so when i'm talking about
wanting to make the content of this show shift beyond just talking about the news if that's what i'm
talking about i want to shift us to be more in alignment with how we get more in alignment
you